[
  {
    "question": "In Marketing, Noon Nopi is _________.",
    "answers": ["all of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The key difference between Marketing and International Marketing is that in International Marketing you are ___________.",
    "answers": ["adding a market abroad"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Etic emphasizes _______ understanding while Emic emphasizes _______ and context specific understanding.",
    "answers": ["culture-free : culture-bound"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The 4P’s of Marketing are _________.",
    "answers": ["Product, Price, Place, and Promotion"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Marketing Execution is __________.",
    "answers": ["noon Nopi realized"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is something we can learn from adaptive organisms?",
    "answers": ["Add more function to survive"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A common problem when asking the question \"what business a company is in\", is that __________.",
    "answers": [
      "some companies limit themselves to what they produce and not what they compete against"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the \"Strategic Intent\" phase of the innovation process, the most important aspect is __________.",
    "answers": [
      "to have an open mindset and allow the pursuit of new technologies"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In Cross Industry Innovation, you can __________.",
    "answers": ["source ideas from other industries"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Transing is.....",
    "answers": ["Bridging of domains to cope with change."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Brands __________.",
    "answers": ["all of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is not a part of Asiana-Cobra Analysis Platform?",
    "answers": ["Snake"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not on the checklist for branding cross country extension?",
    "answers": ["Shareholders’ dividends"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Cross Industry Branding is ________.",
    "answers": [
      "testing of Noon Nopi of brands in multiple industries/products"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Amazon’s goal to be earth’s most customer-centric company is an example of _______.",
    "answers": ["overarching vision"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is the benefit of the \"Fit\" part of Transing's \"Flexible Fit\" concept?",
    "answers": ["Maintaining existing strengths"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Occurrences at the margin of significant environmental change or megatrend are called ____________.",
    "answers": ["Weak signals"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a Transing domain?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Underestimating Noon Nopi can lead to _________.",
    "answers": ["bad word of mouth"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a correct pairing from Hofstede’s Model?",
    "answers": ["Masculinity-femininity : Differentiated gender roles"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is not a cost of Global (Extended) branding across industries?",
    "answers": ["Helping of the parent brand"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Brands are important because they _________.",
    "answers": ["create preferential demand"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A concern for global (standardized) branding in international marketing is",
    "answers": ["Confused buyers if brands formerly had different names"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main reason why we Brand?",
    "answers": ["To help identify and differentiate a product"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Cognitive Distance _____",
    "answers": [
      "Is optimized by balancing the increased novelty and the decreased absorptive capacity"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a type of Marketing Tsunami?",
    "answers": ["Astrological"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Global Marketing is _________.",
    "answers": ["unifying different markets into one Noon Nopi"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Price can be varied by ________.",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a cultural dimension according to Hofstede?",
    "answers": ["Individualism"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is not a characteristic of Marketing Myopia?",
    "answers": ["Thinking of Long term gain over Short Term risk"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the right process of the framework?",
    "answers": ["Vision - Strategy – Action"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The SFU Grid is used for positioning against __________.",
    "answers": ["Competitors"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The country that has opinion Leadership/Trend-setting power on other countries is called _____________.",
    "answers": ["Lead Countries"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Please choose the right sequence of the market selection process.",
    "answers": [
      "Home vs. abroad -> regional selection -> country selection -> segment selection"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A good reason for companies to go abroad is ____________.",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Please select the right sequence of the target selection process 1. Align selection with your VSA 2. Balance the selection criteria 3. Aggregate your segments 4. Backup “Plan A” with “Plan B”",
    "answers": ["1-2-4-3"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A product is _________.",
    "answers": ["Not just tangible but also intangible"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Lego created a face for their brand by utilizing _________.",
    "answers": ["Trans media storytelling"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A way that Place can help Promotion is by __________.",
    "answers": ["The use of flagship stores"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Value equals ________.",
    "answers": ["Benefits/Costs"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When determining relative value in pricing, it is important to approach total benefits and costs by comparing your company to _________.",
    "answers": ["Competitors"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is true about Cross Industry Social Marketing?",
    "answers": ["Social is social no matter online or offline"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In Cross Country Product Marketing, it is important to not __________.",
    "answers": [
      "assume that the mix of tangible and intangible aspects will be the same across countries"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Screen Marketing can be ____________.",
    "answers": ["product placement in movies"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In Small Marketing, it is important to keep in mind that _________.",
    "answers": [
      "small markets and investments can be influential and have huge potential if targeting is done well"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Profiling can help us in terms of understanding ____________ and guiding ____________.",
    "answers": ["consumers, marketing strategies"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When aligning your STP with your VSA, it is important to keep in mind that ___________.",
    "answers": ["your vision requires future orientation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Please choose the best answer. In Market Landing Strategy, a Beachhead Market is ___________.",
    "answers": [
      "the market you strategically start with so that it will help with the future launch of your product in other countries."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is true of the Consumer Journey alignment with Marketing Strategy?",
    "answers": [
      "Marketers should proactively guide their consumers and help them clear through the hurdles at each stage of the journey."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In Price Marketing, Price can help Promotion ____________.",
    "answers": ["all of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In Cross Industry Sports Marketing, it is important to differentiate _____________.",
    "answers": ["spectator vs. participant"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When the VSA Module is utilized on a targeted consumer, the underlying consumer behavioral constructs are ___________.",
    "answers": ["what drives the responses we get from our consumers"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is true in Cross Industry Place Marketing?",
    "answers": ["New technology helps efficiency of service add-ons."]
  },
  {
    "question": "In Market Targeting, which of the following is a criteria that should be balanced?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When positioning against competitors it is good to _________.",
    "answers": [
      "push out weak associations, pull up your SUU associations for POP, and pump up your SFU associations for POD"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Please pick the best answer. What is Skip Marketing?",
    "answers": [
      "The leapfrogging of technology in developing markets due to technology becoming more accessible and less costly over time."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is true when adjusting Noon Nopi to the Bottom of the Pyramid?",
    "answers": ["Trust is important in developing countries."]
  },
  {
    "question": "An orange juice company providing a coupon for bacon is an example of _________.",
    "answers": ["cross promotion"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a good practice when attempting radical repositioning?",
    "answers": [
      "Make a movie to construct and produce a creative narrative for your company."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT Simple Marketing?",
    "answers": ["Divergence"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When comparing “Product” between Tier 1 and Tier 5 of the Pyramid, it is important to know that __________.",
    "answers": [
      "service is usually an augmented product that can help in increasing price in Tier 1 but might be a hard-to-sell proposition in Tier 5"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A positive way that Product can help Price is ________.",
    "answers": ["product quality can increase price"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When the B2B process is formalized, early vendor involvement is good because __________.",
    "answers": [
      "the window of opportunity gets smaller as you wait longer to enter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In B2B2C Pull and Push, _________.",
    "answers": ["pull enabled push strategy can make marketing easier"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Selling Centers are important because salespersons __________.",
    "answers": ["may need cross-functional integration"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Total Marketing is when __________.",
    "answers": ["all of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The different roles of a Buying Center consists of departments and positions but also the ___________.",
    "answers": ["Influencer, Initiator, Gatekeeper, and Decider"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Total Costs of Ownership (TCO), ___________.",
    "answers": [
      "includes the lifetime costs that the owner of a product must deal with"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT true? Personal selling considerations include, _________.",
    "answers": [
      "segmenting amongst our customers to find out which segments we should just drop completely since only focusing on one segment is the best strategy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT true when building the Value Stack?",
    "answers": ["None of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In B2B Promotion Marketing, _________.",
    "answers": [
      "much like boxing, the proper communication steps should be set up before the closing knockout punch"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Channel costs in B2B Marketing, ___________.",
    "answers": ["indirect channels have lower fixed costs"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Going abroad can allow/require your company to…?",
    "answers": ["…all of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Selling Centers are important because salespersons _____?",
    "answers": ["May need cross functional integration"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How are boxing and promotion related?",
    "answers": [
      "Like in boxing, promotion also demands a combination of different “punches” to set up the buyer for business"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In order to “win” in promotion, you have to gain (1)_____, gain (2)______, and gain (3)______ before being able to \"close\" with Action.",
    "answers": ["Attention….interest….desire"]
  },
  {
    "question": "B2B promotion should generally not _____?",
    "answers": ["rely on one tool for promotion"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When expanding abroad, it is important to _____?",
    "answers": ["Consider your supply vendor qualification"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A measuring tool for differences in local business culture to consider is called _____?",
    "answers": ["Hofstede Cultural Dimension Theory"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is one of the key implications of the Total Product System (TPS)?",
    "answers": ["Pre-marketing can lock-in buyers"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In B2B marketing, it is important to focus on _____?",
    "answers": [
      "Both buyer’s benefits and costs analysis as well as your own cost portfolio"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a feature of pricing in the price concept?",
    "answers": ["Price is value that may involve non-price factors also"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In cross country growth, some of the opportunities that we could see are _____?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In determining the total value of your offering in B2B pricing it is important to consider _____?",
    "answers": ["The POP and POD of your benefits and and costs"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Total Costs of Ownership (TCO) refers to _____?",
    "answers": [
      "The aggregate of direct and indirect costs a customer has to bear over the lifetime of a product's use"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In determining a sales and distribution strategy, it is important to consider that _____?",
    "answers": [
      "Different types of customers call for different types of distribution and sales strategy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "With low cultural distance, what is generally the best way to grow to a new country?",
    "answers": ["Locally Produce"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What plays a key role in place marketing?",
    "answers": [
      "It is important to consider the set of service add-ons to help smooth out seller and buyer Noon Nopi gaps"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In determining a channel strategy _____?",
    "answers": ["We should first determine the buyer’s service needs"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An important aspect in B2B Pricing is adding value. What are some important features of adding value?",
    "answers": ["Answers (1) and (2) only"]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the B2B Definition-based Growth Matrix, what is an example of a new diagonal?",
    "answers": ["New application, new product"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The ideal segment cost portfolio is ______.",
    "answers": ["A predominantly low cost and high price"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of the following does not belong to the hospitality industry?",
    "answers": ["Hospitals"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the common characteristics of businesses in the hospitality industry? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Relatively fixed capacity",
      "Perishable inventory",
      "Highly time-variable demand",
      "Low fixed cost and high variable cost"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Most hospitality businesses sell through advance reservations. What are the upsides of this characteristic? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Can act proactively about balancing supply and demand.",
      "Can better predict demand."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "One of the common characteristics of hospitality businesses is that their market is segmentable. In other words, customers can be grouped into different segments. What are the important differences among different segments that matter to the successful marketing of the business? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Difference in the preferred time of consumption",
      "Difference in the perceived value of an essentially same product",
      "Difference in the flexibility with the time of consumption",
      "Difference in the ability to plan in advance",
      "Difference in the level of uncertainty of the use"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill in the blanks in the following sentence: Variable pricing approach recommends that businesses charge different prices to different customers for essentially same product because different customers are willing to pay different prices due to different ___ (one word)___ and ___(two words)___ of the product.",
    "answers": ["valuations and perceived values"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How does variable pricing approach increase revenue compared to using fixed pricing approach? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "By capturing more demand by charging lower prices to those who are not willing pay regular prices",
      "By charging a higher price to customers who are willing to pay higher price"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is it true or false. Preventing customers who are willing to pay a higher price from paying a lower price is the biggest challenge in successfully moving from fixed pricing to variable pricing.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the rate fence in variable pricing? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "It is a set of conditions that have to be satisfied in order for a lower price to be allowed.",
      "It is a set of characteristics that distinguish customers from one segment from another."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Chef's table is an example of ______________________.",
    "answers": ["Premium pricing"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is it true or false? Broad-scale discounting is a bad idea because it makes people who are willing to pay a higher price pay a lower price.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A weekend get-away package for locals is a good example of ___________.",
    "answers": ["Target discounting"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence true or false? Coordination of efforts between marketing team and operations team is an essential component for the successful implementation of target discounting.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of the following is not true of the healthcare industry?",
    "answers": ["It is one of the most profitable industries in the world."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of the following is not the aspect that distinguishes the healthcare industry from other service industries?",
    "answers": ["Customers' assessment of the outcome is very objective."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of the following does the malpractice example used in the lecture illustrate the importance of managing?",
    "answers": ["Doctor's interaction with patients"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence true or false? It is the patient experience beyond patient service that has to be well managed for competitive advantage in the healthcare industry.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Easy access to the healthcare facility, shortened waiting time, and friendly staff compose which one of the following qualities of healthcare services?",
    "answers": ["Value-added service quality"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Managing patient experience requires care that addresses every aspect of the patient's encounter with the clinic including ___________. Choose all the words that can fill in this blank.",
    "answers": [
      "Emotional needs",
      "Spiritual needs",
      "Educational needs",
      "Physical comfort."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Shouldice Hospital was shown as a good example of a hospital with a successful patient experience design and management. Why was offering only double-occupancy rooms considered a good idea for managing patience experience?",
    "answers": [
      "Because it can help patients help each other address emotional needs."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does managing patients' interactions with others in the hospital matter to the hospital?",
    "answers": [
      "Because the quality of the interactions influence patients' satisfaction with the service at the hospital"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence true or false? It is not only the direct interactions but also indirect interactions of patients with others in the hospital that influence patients' satisfaction.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the case of in-patients, which one of the following is a good idea to faciliate interactions among patients? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Group exercise sessions",
      "Patient orientation program at the beginning of the hospitalization process"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of the following is not a key design element of healthcare facilities? Choose all.",
    "answers": ["None of above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the \"positive distraction\" as a design element of healthcare facilities?",
    "answers": [
      "Simple distraction of patient attention from worries, concerns and pains"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The stethoscope shaped like a teddy bear is a good example of _______-centered healthcare. What is the right word to fill in this blank?",
    "answers": ["Patient"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When a customer buys a service product, compared to buying a goods product, what does the customer really buy?",
    "answers": ["Benefits"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of the following is not a unique characteristic of services?",
    "answers": ["Credibility"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the management challenges associated with the fact that customers are present, participate, or co-create values during the service delivery process? Choose the two most applicable ones.",
    "answers": [
      "Designing the physical environment (servicescape) of the service delivery",
      "Designing the role of customers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is balancing supply and demand so challenging for services? Choose the two most applicable causes.",
    "answers": [
      "Because demand is highly time-variable while supply is relatively fixed over time.",
      "Because services cannot be pre-produced and inventoried."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Offering service guarantees to customers is a way to preempt customer demand. What is the unique characteristic of services that triggers service managers' interest in offering such guarantees?",
    "answers": ["Heterogeneity"]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the lecture, what causes customer evaluation to differ so widely across different customers for an identical service delivered by the same person in the same way at the same level of quality?",
    "answers": ["Customer expectation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How is a service customer's satisfaction determined?",
    "answers": [
      "By the difference between customer expectation and customer perception"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence true or false? In managing the quality of service, prevention is the only way to ensure quality.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence true or false? Early bird specials offered by a restaurant are a way to cope with the perishability characteristic of a service business.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence true or false? Service customers use servicescape as a clue for the quality of service.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence true or false? Airlines are better off by selling airplane seats, which would otherwise go unsold, at a price higher than the variable cost of selling a seat than not selling it at all.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence true or false? Perceived service quality is same as the reality of the service.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is one of the guidelines for country/city sports marketing?",
    "answers": ["Determining the SFU associations"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is NOT one of the 4 A’s of Sports Sponsorship?",
    "answers": ["Achievement"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is NOT an example of a long term objective of sponsorship?",
    "answers": ["Meet competitive threats"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an aspect of formulating a good narrative?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is BIRGing?",
    "answers": ["Basking in related glory"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is true about creating fandom?",
    "answers": [
      "There needs to be history, tradition and authenticity, as well as entertainment value"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Awareness in sports sponsorship increases when____?",
    "answers": ["Brand awareness is well maintained"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some aspects of cross country sports marketing?",
    "answers": ["Growth can be as a product or medium"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a characteristic of cross industry sports marketing?",
    "answers": ["Sports can be a source or a destination of innovation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an example of sports importing?",
    "answers": ["Virtual and Augmented Reality"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In Entertainment Marketing, Netflix matched Noon Nopi of ___________ and Steve Jobs matched Noon Nopi of ____________.",
    "answers": ["binge viewing, attention holding"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is FALSE?",
    "answers": [
      "There can be many sources for big ideas",
      "there can be many sources for big ideas"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In Cross Country Entertainment market configuration it is important ____________.",
    "answers": [
      "to keep in mind that some products will have a broader appeal in some countries and a narrower appeal in others"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of Entertainment Exporting?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Any business can technically be like Show Business as long as it is ____________.",
    "answers": [
      "entertaining, engagaing, boundary-breaking, and value co-creating"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a Marketing implication of OTT TV?",
    "answers": [
      "Segmentation, targeting and positioning must focus on Millennials watching TV online"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Making brands ownable means ____________.",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In cross country entertainment, it is important to remember that ___________.",
    "answers": ["the landing market is important"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT an example of Entertainment Importing?",
    "answers": ["Experience reduction"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT an advantage of placement?",
    "answers": [
      "Higher defense against attention to brands by consumers",
      "Higher defense against attention to a brand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Creativity is about aligning __________ and __________ to solve problems.",
    "answers": ["idea, execution"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Over the Top TV?",
    "answers": [
      "Direct to consumer internet delivery of content without need for cable/satellite subscriptions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is False? In entertainment, content ___________.",
    "answers": ["is becoming a key issue offline but not online"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Show Business Brand Relationship Model, you have consumers create, participate, interact, and experience the element of Show Business through _________.",
    "answers": ["the brand"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is holding attention among a \"crowd of one\" important in entertainment?",
    "answers": [
      "Because with online media a crowd of one can ultimately be a crowd of many."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Disney's practice of having even their top executives don costumes has the intended effect of...",
    "answers": [
      "Making them experience the joy and difficulty of engaging customers firsthand."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the key benefit of a technology like a Hologram when used for a concert?",
    "answers": [
      "You can have a broader global reach in a more engaging and life-like way."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "With viral marketing why does crowdsourcing ideas need to be controlled?",
    "answers": [
      "Because the ideas from crowds may not match the vision and strategy of the creative content."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In OTT TV, cannibalization for cable TV companies means...",
    "answers": [
      "The loss of their subscribers and viewers for their cable channels if they offer OTT TV themselves."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Local Adaptation of sports sponsorship increases when___?",
    "answers": [
      "There is a good balance between global and local sensibilities"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In trying to obtain fandom, sports teams can employ which model for guidance?",
    "answers": ["Fan Identification Model"]
  },
  {
    "question": "One way of measuring influence from an individual athlete is ____?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a characteristic of storytelling?",
    "answers": ["Storytelling is limited to sports"]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to John Davis, why is sports marketing so important in branding?",
    "answers": [
      "Because through fandom, there are deeper positive associations and loyalty"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The line between a spectator and a participant in sports overlaps..",
    "answers": ["Depending on the sport."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Because different consumers in sports seek different benefits, the key marketing implication is__________",
    "answers": ["We need to match the Noon Nopi to the specific consumer."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not one of the \"4M's\" of Influence Marketing?",
    "answers": ["Monopolize"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is the analogy of a small fish appropriate to understand sports sponsorship?",
    "answers": [
      "Because a sponsor is like a small fish who wants to use a bigger fish, a sport, that ultimately attracts the attention of the biggest fish, the global consumer."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you as a sporting organization have the vision to make sports more affordable to fans, which of the following strategies and actions is NOT aligned with that VSA?",
    "answers": ["Build more VIP Sky boxes to earn higher revenues."]
  },
  {
    "question": "When dealing with Consumer Behavior, it is important to ___________.",
    "answers": [
      "Understand consumers at the individual level and also their collective influences"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When utilizing VSA on a target consumer, the key objective is ____________.",
    "answers": [
      "To ensure alignment of response, consumer constructs, and marketing action"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When marketing to the “Bottom of the Pyramid” it is important to ____________.",
    "answers": [
      "Remember that different tiers respond to marketing actions in a different way"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Marketing CSI is _____________.",
    "answers": [
      "The art of gathering data and putting the pieces together to create a profile of your Noon Nopi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In Hidden Consumer Behavior, ____________ is a construct that occurs deep inside the minds of people.",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In cross country social marketing, it is important to remember that __________.",
    "answers": ["O2O can mean online to offline but also offline to online"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In cross industry Simple Marketing, the search for similarity between industries in order to simplify must be done in a ___________.",
    "answers": ["Multi-level way"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Small Marketing is ________.",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In cross country Skip Marketing, __________.",
    "answers": ["None of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An important factor in cross country Screen Marketing, is ________.",
    "answers": ["The universality of the star of the movie"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Set Marketing is about complementary products, which are ________.",
    "answers": [
      "Products that do not compete with each other",
      "products that do not compete with each other"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sports Marketing is the ________.",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A common misperception of B2B Marketing is that _______.",
    "answers": ["B2B Marketing is rather simple when compared to B2C Marketing"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Please choose the right explanation. In B2B Marketing, _____________.",
    "answers": ["all of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In B2B Marketing, __________.",
    "answers": [
      "relationships matter more so than in B2C Marketing because there are fewer and larger customers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The 4W’s in the 4W Approach ________.",
    "answers": [
      "includes the weight or voice that the member of the buying center carries"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In B2B Marketing, the member of the Buying Center that controls the access or information to other members such as the key decision maker is known as the __________.",
    "answers": ["gatekeeper"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In B2B product variation __________.",
    "answers": [
      "hybrid products enjoy the advantages of costs and perceived value"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In advertising, vertical vehicles are _________.",
    "answers": ["specialized to one industry"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following it NOT a component In B2B2C Pricing?",
    "answers": ["None of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of direct selling?",
    "answers": ["Online selling from the manufacturer's website"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is true about Total Product System (TPS) Marketing?",
    "answers": ["Pre-marketing can lock-in buyers"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is creating a customer-fiendly environment important in services?",
    "answers": ["Because customers participate in the service delivery process"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is not true of service recovery?",
    "answers": ["Service recovery has to be avoided at all costs."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence true or false? When managing service operations, not only the real quality of services but also customer expectations and perceptions for service quality have to be managed.",
    "answers": ["true"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence true of false? In services, it is better to sell than not selling at all as long as prices are higher than variable costs of selling that unit.",
    "answers": ["false"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence true or false? In services, customers co-create the services. A college course designed as a lecture is a good example of a service co-created with customers.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "One of the characteristics of the hospitality industry is relatively fixed capacity. What is not the right example of this characteristic?",
    "answers": ["None of above."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why can charging one fixed price for an essentially same service product be a bad idea? Choose an answer that does not offer the right reason.",
    "answers": ["Because customers perceive fixed pricing as unfair."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a rate fence? Choose the answer that is not correct.",
    "answers": ["Rate fence is optional."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence true or false? Broad-scale discounting is more effective than target pricing in maximizing revenue through discounting.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence true or false? Premium pricing is charging a higher price to customers who are willing to pay a higher price for an essentially same product with no particular premium features.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Healthcare industry has evolved from competing on the technical quality into competing on the added value service quality. What does healthcare businesses compete on now?",
    "answers": ["Holistic patient experience quality"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following aspects of Shouldice Hospital relates to patient experience management? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Shouldice offers beautiful garden.",
      "Shouldice serves patients with the same food as hospital staff.",
      "Shouldice does not place a TV set in the patient room."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence true or false? Facilitating patient's interaction with service providers has long been the focus of healthcare management, but facilitating patient's interaction with other patients or family members has not been.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence true or false? Kameda Medical Center offers a beauty salon and a pet lounge in order to enhance patient experience.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence true or false? Hospitals place artworks or big windows with good views to distract patient attention from pains.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of these is a main customer of sports?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In consideration of the 4 Ps, which of the following could best be an aspect of the Product?",
    "answers": ["Parking"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which option best describes a fan?",
    "answers": [
      "A customer of an athlete or sports organization with personal commitment and emotional involvement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The main driver of influence marketing through athletes is _____?",
    "answers": ["Trust"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In sports marketing, specifically storytelling, _____?",
    "answers": ["The story needs to be easily remembered"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a factor in finding a globally-resonant common denominator?",
    "answers": ["Global markets are cluttered with established brands"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The Show Biz VSA Mapping is an effective way _____________.",
    "answers": [
      "for companies to utilize elements of show business to help their vision, strategy and action."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a placement disadvantage?",
    "answers": ["Low absolute cost"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is true about creativity?",
    "answers": ["creativity is problem solving"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is TRUE about virtual reality's potential?",
    "answers": ["There are many Cross Industry Application Possibilities"]
  }
]
